http://www.hedkandi.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to the content
Privacy Policy
www.hedkandi.com  is operated by Ministry of Sound Group Limited trading as Hed Kandi and adheres to the MOS privacy policy.
MOS Privacy PolicyMinistry of Sound Group Limited ("MOS") a company registered in England and Wales with registration number 032996686 and registered office at 103 Gaunt Street, London, SE1 6DP, United Kingdom.
The terms "we", "our", "us" when used in this Privacy Policy means MOS. The terms "you", "your" and "yours" means you as a user of our websites or our other services.Please read the following Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") carefully before submitting any personal information to us. Any information you provide about yourself to MOS or our associated companies will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy1.1 From time to time, we may need to make changes to this Privacy Policy. This may happen as a result of government regulation, new technologies, or other developments in our online or other services. Any updates to our Privacy Policy will be clearly posted in this section of our website. We advise you to regularly review this policy when you visit our websites to keep informed about how we are safeguarding your privacy. If the changes are significant, we may also email you to notify you about these.1.2 Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to websites or text services operated by third parties and you are advised to check such third party privacy policies before submitting data to them.
Our Aims2.1 We are fully committed to protecting your privacy and will respect your privacy in connection with any email, mobile or other personal details you submit to us via any media.2.2 We will not collect personally identifying information (such as your name, address, email address etc.) except with your specific knowledge and consent or as detailed within this Privacy Policy.2.3 We work closely with our technology partners and other suppliers to ensure that your personal information is protected with high quality, reliable and secure technology. Our technology partners invest in high-quality security and work hard to protect your privacy.2.4 We follow strict security procedures in compliance with UK Data Protection legislation governing the storage and disclosure of information given by you to us via our websites, your mobile or other media.
Collection and use of information3.1 It will normally be clear when your personal information is being collected. The personal information we will collect depends on how you are interacting with our websites or otherwise but may include, amongst other things, your name, postal address (including post code), telephone number, email address, age, gender, password and, for transactions, financial details.3.2 We may ask different questions or request additional information depending on the service being offered to or requested by you. Unless stated, all questions are compulsory. We may also ask some further, voluntary questions so we can gain a clearer understanding of our users.3.3 We collect personal information only for specific limited purposes and we only ask for information that is appropriate. We will only collect personal information from you which you have provided by completing any registration, enquiry, order or application form on our websites, or which you have sent to us via email, fax or post or which you have provided by telephone or any other means. We also collect information on our users through cookies on websites (see our Cookies Policy), interactions with our websites and our text services and via other media.3.4 By disclosing your personal information to us, you agree that we may obtain, hold and use the personal information you provide for the purposes of providing you with our services and/or products and with ancillary services (the "Purposes"). The Purposes for which personal information is collected and processed include, without limitation:(a) responding to any enquiries you have made;(b) sending you materials and/or information you have requested or products which you have purchased;(c) performing our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us;(d) conducting contests, competitions or promotions;(e) enabling you to submit contributions to us (for example, for use on our websites);(f) to customise and improve the content on our websites or any other websites which are part of the MOS Group and/or to improve our products and services to respond to your current and future needs and interests;(g) contacting you if we change our products or services or terms or if we need to give you notice of them;(h) for the purpose of marketing our other products and services to you (for example, by email, text or post) unless you indicate otherwise during the submission process (for example, by ticking the relevant boxes that are provided) or by subsequently notifying us as set out in Sections 3.11 and 9.1 that you do not wish to receive such material;(i) for accounting purposes and internal administration and analysis;(j) for the prevention of fraud; and(k) for any purpose required by law or regulation.3.5 The information we need depends on how you are interacting with our website, text service or otherwise, but could include by way of example an email address, password, age, gender and postcode and a mobile telephone number.3.6 You may be invited to register with us when you interact with us (for example, via our websites). Any registration is voluntary and entirely your choice. However, you may be unable to visit certain parts of our website or enter some of our competitions if you do not register.3.7 If you have registered with us (for example, if you have become a member of parts of our websites), we may e-mail, mail, text or otherwise contact you, as appropriate, with information about your registration and/or offers or competitions open to you as a registered member.3.8 From time to time we may run competitions or request material for publication or broadcast. To participate, you must usually supply us with your identity which you agree to have publicly associated with your submission. The exact rules vary from case to case, and will be noted clearly on the relevant pages (e.g. our website terms and conditions relating to submission of material or in the relevant competition terms and conditions).3.9 You should be aware that any information or material you post in public areas on our websites (such as message boards) may be seen, collected and used by others, and may result in unsolicited messages from other users or parties. Alas, we can't control this; you post at your own risk. Please see our website terms and conditions at [insert link] for further information.3.10 Any research carried out via our websites is for the exclusive use of MOS unless specifically stated at the time of completion. Your response to research request is voluntary. However, please note that "pooled" responses to questions may be shared with our partner organisations.3.11 If you wish to unsubscribe from emails and/or other communications sent by MOS, you may do so at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link that appears in our email messages or by contacting us
Disclosure of personal information4.1 Subject to the terms set out in this Privacy Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or distribute personal data to or with third parties (for example, sponsors and advertisers) unless the transfer of such information to third parties is strictly necessary for the performance of the Purposes (e.g. for fulfilling a request you may have made of us) and we will not disclose personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have consented to this.4.2 We may share personal information with other companies within the MOS Group of companies which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985 in connection with the Purposes and the operation of the Website. We may disclose personal information to service providers who manage aspects of our operations for example third parties who provide technical services to the site.4.3 We may share your personal information with other third party companies where you have expressly consented to this.4.4 We may disclose your personal information if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce our website or other terms and conditions, or to protect the rights, property, security or safety of MOS, other websites, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with our companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.4.5 Information about you and your use of our websites may help us to sell appropriate advertising space to third parties and we may share anonymous aggregate statistics about our users, sales and traffic patterns with our advertisers. Whilst your individual information is protected as outlined in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group whether this is in connection with either web or text users. For example, we might report to potential advertisers that a certain percentage of our users are interested in its products, based on information requests. In addition, we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.4.6 In the future, we may sell our business or assets. Personal information is usually considered an asset in such transactions. We may disclose, transfer, sell, assign or licence information described in this Privacy Policy, including personally identifiable information, to third parties as a result of or in preparation for the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation of MOS and you consent to such disclosure, transfer, sale, assignment or licence.
Registration5.1 Where you have registered to access certain parts of our websites you will have chosen a password which enables you to access a restricted part of a website. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential and you should not share this with anyone. You are responsible for all use and communications with our websites which take place using your registration or password.
Transfer of personal information outside of the European Economic Area ("EEA")For the reasons set out in this Privacy Policy and for technical and operational reasons, your personal information may from time to time, on our behalf, be transferred, processed or stored on servers based outside of the EEA. You should be aware that such countries outside of the EEA may not offer the same level of protection for your data. For example, your data may be processed to allow personalised radio streaming, to process your entry into a competition, to fullfil any order you make for goods or services, to process any payment details or to provide support services. By submitting data to us you consent to such transfer, storing and processing outside the EEA. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including steps to help ensure that contractors operating on our behalf are subject to our standard technical and security obligations to provide an adequate level of protection for your information.
Security7.1 We use up to date industry procedures and technology to keep personal data as safe and secure as possible and to protect against loss, unauthorised disclosure or access. MOS and our associated companies follow the relevant legal requirements and use all reasonable precautions to ensure only responsible third parties see the information. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or any actions of any third parties who receive the information.7.2 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
The Data Protection Act and the Information Commissioner8.1 In the UK, the Data Protection Act provides a framework for the safety and security of personal data and the uses to which such personal data is put. The Information Commissioner is the UK's independent public body set up to protect personal information and provide information to individuals and organisations. Please see www.ico.gov.uk for more information.8.2 We are registered with the Information Commissioner as a 'data controller' under registration number Z6699303. We will ensure that all personal information supplied by you to us is held and dealt with in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and its relevant subordinate legislation and we will comply with the principles set out in that Act. When you supply any personal information to us we will meet our legal obligations towards you in the way that we deal with that information. In accordance with the data protection principles we must collect personal information fairly and let you know how we will use it and whether we will pass the information on to anyone else. For the avoidance of doubt, we will not supply your personal information to third parties without your express prior consent other than as set out in this Privacy Policy. We will ensure that any information will be held only as long as is necessary to ensure that our service runs smoothly.8.3 The Data Protection Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Updating your information9.1 If you are registered with us, you may update your personal information at any time via the "My Details" page for web users. You can get to the "My Details Page" from most pages on our websites if you are logged-on. In addition if you believe the information we hold about you to be out of date or inaccurate please email us at info@ministryofsound.com or contact us at +44 (0) 20 7740 8600.
Parents10.1 MOS is committed to the safety and privacy of children who visit and participate in our services. For those activities that require us to collect personal information (e.g. competitions), we will only collect personal information which is necessary to enable us to administer the relevant activity. We encourage parents and guardians to watch over their children's online use. Please educate your children to always ask for your permission before they provide personal information.
Children11.1 Remember to be smart and safe online. Always ask your parent or guardian for permission before you give out any personal information. This could include your name, email address, home address, telephone number, your school or any other information about yourself that would enable someone to contact you either online or offline.11.2 From time to time we run online competitions that you may be able to enter. Always remember to ask your parent or guardian for permission before entering any competition.
Home
Privacy Policy
